Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Benson Bond Moore papers
- Photographs, 1924-1971, Series 8:; (Box 5-7, OV 8; 0.7 linear feet)
  - Photographs of Miscellaneous Subjects for Art Work, undated, (Oversized Material Housed in Box 6) (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Photographs of Art Work Depicting Animals, undated, (3 folders) (Box 5, Folder 81-83)
  - Photographs of Art Work Depicting Birds, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 84-85)
  - Photographs of Art Work Depicting Landscapes,undated, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 86-87)
  - Photograph of Miscellaneous Art Work, undated (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Photographs of Art Work by Others, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 89-90)
  - Oversized Photograph of Unidentified Colleague and Three Oversized Photographs of Unidentified Woman, undated, (from Box 5, Folder 62) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Two Oversized Photographs Autographed by Herbert Hoover; Oversized Photograph Autographed by Franklin D. Roosevelt, 1931-1933, undated, (from Box 5, Folder 62) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Two Oversized Photographs of 19th Century Sailors and Battleships at War, undated, (from Box 5, Folder 80) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Oversized Album of Photographs of Art Work, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Panoramic Photograph of Boy on Bicycle, undated, (from Box 5, Folder 59) (Box OV 8)